Guide to the Yale College Ad Hoc Committee on Residential Deanships Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale College Ad Hoc Committee on Residential Deanships records
1974-1975
RU 712
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.5
(1 box)
The records consist of questionnaires, correspondence, minutes, reports, and notes documenting the plans and deliberations of the Yale College Ad Hoc Committee on Residential Deanships.
Yale College (1887- )
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 9-D (YRG 9-D), Records of Yale College committees.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of questionnaires, correspondence, minutes, reports, and notes documenting the plans and deliberations of the Yale College Ad Hoc Committee on Residential Deanships.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by type of material.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Deans (Education); Dormitories; Student housing; Yale College (1887- ); Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Student housing
- Records, 1974-1975; Accession 1975-A-011
  - Questionnaires, Lists, Correspondence
    - Questionnaire to deans, 1974 April (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Responses to questionnaire circulated by committee, 1974 April (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence with past deans, 1974 June-August (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Comments by committee members: TLS Martin Griffith to Charles D. Walker, 1974 August 20 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Committee on residential college deanships: minutes of meetings and notes, 1974 March-September (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Committee on residential college deanships: minutes of meetings, notes and various items, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Proposed introduction to the committee report, by Charles A. Walker, 1974 July (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Draft of report on residential college deanships, 1974 July (Box 1, Folder 8 - 9)
    - Second draft of report on the residential college deanships: transcript and arrangement with corrections, 1974 October (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Third draft of report: typescript with corrections and finished draft, 1974 December (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Report on residential college deanships: typescript with corrections, two copies of final report, 1974 December (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Report of faculty committee given before faculty meeting, 1975 April (Box 1, Folder 13)